A Guide to the Allen Collection of Frank O'Hara Letters 1976.0001
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
Allen Collection of Frank O'Hara Letters
1950-1966
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1976.0001
.75 Linear Feet
Typewritten transcriptions made by Donald Allen of Frank O'Hara letters. Allen collected and transcribed the letters while preparing and editing The Collected Poems of Frank O'Hara.
Scope and Content
Typewritten transcriptions made by Donald Allen of Frank O'Hara letters. Allen collected and transcribed O'Hara's letters while preparing and editing The Collected Poems of Frank O'Hara.
Arrangement
Letters are arranged chronologically by date.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Correspondence; Photocopies; Authors; Beat generation in literature; Beat generation; Schuyler, James; Allen, Donald, 1912-2004; Ginsberg, Allen, 1926-1997; Rosset, Barney; Mitchell, Joan, 1925-1992; Frankenthaler, Helen, 1928-2011; Ashbery, John, 1927-2017; Martory, Pierre; Goldberg, Michael, 1924-2007; Porter, Fairfield; Hartigan, Grace; Corso, Gregory; Berkson, Bill; Osgood, Lawrence, 1929-; Freilicher, Jane, 1924-2014; Rivers, Larry, 1925-2002; Guest, Barbara; Porter, Anne, 1911-2011; Rorem, Ned, 1923-; Koch, Kenneth, 1925-2002; Orlovsky, Peter, 1933-2010
- Series I: Letters, 1950-1966
  - Osgood, Lawrence (from Cambridge), 1950-06-23 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Osgood, Lawrence (from Cambridge), 1950-08-02 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Osgood, Lawrence (from Cambridge), 1950-08-31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Osgood, Lawrence (from Michigan), 1950-09-27 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Osgood, Lawrence (from Michigan), 1950-10-19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Freilicher, Jane (from Michigan), 1951-03-08 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Scouffas, George (from Michigan), 1951-04-24 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Osgood, Lawrence (from Michigan), "late spring" [1951] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Freilicher, Jane (one page out of sequence), "late spring" [1951] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Freilicher, Jane (from Michigan), 1951-06-06 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Freilicher, Jane (from Michigan), 1951-07-06 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rivers, Larry (from Michigan), 1951-07 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Freilicher, Jane (from Michigan), 1951-08-01 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Freilicher, Jane (from Michigan), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Porter, Arabel [Mrs.], 1952-01-16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1952-05 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Freilicher, Jane, 1952-08-08 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Quinn, Kerker, 1953-02-26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1953-06-27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1953-09-16 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Porters, 1953-10-20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fizdale, Robert, 1953-11-03 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fizdale, Robert, 1953-12-26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Feldman, Morton, 1954-01-02 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Porter, Anne, 1954-01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1954-01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Freilicher, Jane, 1954-01-19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1954-02-16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Freilicher, Jane, 1954-02-23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Freilicher, Jane, 1954-03 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Weber, Ben, 1954-03-20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1954-04-20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Quinn, Kerker, 1954-04-27 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Freilicher, Jane, 1954-04 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Porters, 1954-05-01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1954-05-21 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Porter, Fairfield, 1954-06-25 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kanovitz, Howard and Marilyn Meeker, 1954-07-07 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1954-07-13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Porter, Fairfield, 1954-08-05 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1954-08-14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Koch, Kenneth (from O'Hara and Ashbery), 1954-11-26 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Porter, Fairfield, 1955-02-02 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Porters, 1955-04-04 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1955-04-08 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1955-04-22 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1955-05-09 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1955-05-10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1955-05-23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Porters, 1955-06-01 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1955-06-06 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Porter, Fairfield and Anne, 1955-06-09 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Kochs, 1955-06-23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1955-06-30 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Porter, Fairfield, 1955-07-07 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Porter, Fairfield, 1955-07-20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Porters, 1955-08-08 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Guest, Barbara (from Maine with Porters), 1955-08-21 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1955-09-12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Porters, 1955-09-12 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Porters, 1955-10-03 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Porter, Fairfield, 1955-10-07 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Griffin, Howard, 1955-10-14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Montgomery, George, 1955-11-09 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Weber, Ben, 1955-11-14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - LeSueur, Joe, 1956-01-05 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Kochs (from Cambridge), 1956-01-09 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hartigan, Grace (from Cambridge), 1956-01-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Porters (from Cambridge), 1956-01-26 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hartigan, Grace (from Cambridge), 1956-01-30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rosset, Barney (from Cambridge), 1956-02-07 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hartigan, Grace (from Cambridge), 1956-02-10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Schuyler, James (from Cambridge), 1956-02-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Kochs (from Cambridge), 1956-02-12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Goldberg, Michael (from Cambridge), 1956-02-16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rosset, Barney (from Cambridge), 1956-02-29 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Koch, Kenneth (from Cambridge), 1956-04 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rosset, Barney (from Cambridge), 1956-04-09 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rosset, Barney (from Cambridge), 1956-04-18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Koch, Kenneth (from Cambridge), 1956-04 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rosset, Barney (from Cambridge), 1956-05-02 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mitchell, Joan (from Cambridge), 1956-05-04 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Koch, Kenneth (from Cambridge), 1956-05-06 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Button, John, 1956-06-12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Schuyler, James (from Sandwich, New Hampshire), 1956-06-15 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Weber, Ben (from Cambridge), 1956-06-18 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1956-06-26 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Weber, Ben (from Cambridge), 1956-08-02 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rosset, Barney, 1956-08-16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Osgood, Larry, 1956-08-20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rosset, Barney, 1956-08-21 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rosset, Barney, 1956-09-19 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1956-09-28 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1956-10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Kochs, 1956-12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Shattuck, Roger, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1957-01-07 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Kochs, 1957-01-10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Schmidt, Judith, 1957-01-18 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Porter, Arabel, 1957-01-29 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Kochs, 1957-01-29 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ashbery, John, 1957-03-27 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Weiss, Ted, 1957-03-28 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1957-04-08 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1957-04-08 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rosset, Barney, 1957-05-13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ashbery, John, 1957-05-14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1957-06-03 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1957-06-10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1957-06-12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1957-07-02 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1957-07-16 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Kochs, 1957-07-25 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ashbery, John, 1957-07-24 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Goldberg, Mike, 1957-08-26 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allen, Don, 1957-08-27 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1957-09-19 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1957-12-20 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allen, Don, 1958-02-10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1958-03-09 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Corso, Gregory, 1958-03-20 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hurley, Irma, 1958-04-21 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allen, Don, 1958-05-18 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Editors of Encounter, 1958-05-20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Schmidt, Judith, 1958-05-20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1958-06-16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allen, Don, 1958-07-16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fondren, Hal, 1958-07-19 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hartigan, Grace (from Rome), 1958-08-19 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allen, Don (from Rome), 1958-08-20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1958-09-14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ashbery, John, 1958-10-10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1958-11-11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ashbery, John, 1958-12-19 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ashbery, John, 1958-12-22 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Corso, Gregory, 1958-12-29 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - LeSueur, Joe (from Paris), 1959-01-17 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ashbery, John, 1959-01-28 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Corso, Gregory, 1959-02-11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1959-02-20 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ashbery, John and Pierre Martory, 1959-03-16 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Allen, Don, 1959-03-25 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1959-04-20 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1959-05-27 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ginsberg, Allen and Peter Orlovsky, 1959-06-01 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1959-06-04 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ashbery, John and Pierre Martory, 1959-07-14 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell, Joan, 1959-07-27 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Kochs and James Schuyler, 1959-08-11 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Schuyler, James, 1959-08-12 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1959-08-17 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Kochs, 1959-08-31 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cable to Nell Blaine, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1959-09-02 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ashbery, John and Pierre Martory, 1959-10-02 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mitchell, Joan, 1959-10-02 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Martory, Pierre, 1959-10-06 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ashbery, John, 1959-10-13 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1959-10-16 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1959-10-19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ashbery, John, 1959-10-29 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mitchell, Joan, 1959-11-12 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1959-12-04 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Mitchell, Joan, 1959-12-07 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1959-12-16 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1959-12-18 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1959-12-18 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Schuyler, James, 1959-12-23 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ashbery, John, 1959-12-30 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation Statement, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Allen, Don, 1960-01-13 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-03-08 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-03-14 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-03-17 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Warren, Vincent (from Spain), 1960-03-23 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Allen, Don, 1960-03-23 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1960-03-23 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-03-26 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-04-02 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Witt-Diamant, Ruth, 1960-04-25 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Allen, Don, 1960-04-28 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-04 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-05-09 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Grosman, Tatyana, 1960-05-13 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1960-05-13 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-06-20 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-06-23 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-06-24 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-06-27 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-06-28 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-06-30 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-01 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-06 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-07 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-11 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Allen, Don, 1960-07-12 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-07-14 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-14 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-17 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-18 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-26 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hartigan, Grace, 1960-07-27 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Koch, Kenneth, 1960-07-28 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1960-07-29 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-07-29 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-08-02 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1960-08-05 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1960-08-10 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1960-08-11 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Allen, Don, 1960-09-12 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-09-21 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-09-30 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ashbery, John, 1960-10-14 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Rorem, Ned, 1960-12-21 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-01-16 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-01-17 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-01-18 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-01-23 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Witt-Diamant, Ruth, 1961-01-25 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Don, 1961-01-27 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-01-27 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Witt-Diamant, Ruth, 1961-01-30 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-02-01 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Don, 1961-02-08 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-02-09 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-02-10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1961-02-13 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-02-14 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mitchell, Joan, 1961-02-23 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-02-27 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-02-28 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-03-01 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-03-02 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-03-04 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-03-06 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-03-08 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Orlovsky, Peter, 1961-03-23 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-05-01 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1961-05-19 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1961-05-22 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-06-07 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-06-22 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1961-07-05 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1961-07-05 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-07-10 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-07-17 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1961-07-18 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-07-18 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-07-21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1961-07-21 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Guest, Barbara, 1961-07-24 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1961-07-24 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1961-07-28 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Miller, Richard, 1961-07-28 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-08-17 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Boneham, Peter, 1961-08-25 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1961-09-07 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-09-20 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Allen, Don, 1961-09-20 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-09-20 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-09-29 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-10-16 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Open Letter in support of Floating Bear, 1961-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Rivers, Larry (from Rome), 1961-11-11 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ashbery, John, 1961-12-07 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-12-10 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Allen, Don, 1961-12-15 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1961-12-17 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1961-12-18 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-01-02 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-01-03 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-01-08 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Ashbery, John, 1962-01-08 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-01-15 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Warren, Vincent, 2017-01-19 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Berkson, Bill, 1962-01-31 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-02-05 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Boneham, Peter, 1962-02-11 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-02-15 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-03-02 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ashbery, John, 1962-03-09 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-03-13 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-03-15 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-03-23 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ashbery, John, 1962-04-11 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Ashbery, John, 1962-04-20 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-04-27 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-05-28 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-06-11 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Grosman, Tanya, 1962-06-20 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Berkson, Bill, 1962-07-10 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-07-30 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Berkson, Bill, 1962-08-12 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Allen, Don, 1962-08-18 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Shapiro, David, 1962-09-10 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Ashbery, John, 1962-09-11 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-10-04 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-10-27 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1962-10-29 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Mitchell, Joan, 1962-11-11 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Ashbery, John, 1962-11-20 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Shapiro, David, 1962-12-03 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-12-03 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Shapiro, David, 1962-12-06 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1962-12-30 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - O'Hara, Philip, 1963-01-11 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1963-01-12 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1963-01-18 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Lima, Frank, 1963-02-06 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Ashbery, John, 1963-02-07 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Berkson, Bill, 1963-02-19 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Groffsky, Maxine, 1963-03-16 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Malanga, Gerard, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1963-04-07 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1963-04-20 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1963-05-15 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1963-06-04 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Ashbery, John, 1963-06-14 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1963-06-19 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1963-06-30 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1963-07-21 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Allen, Don, 1963-08-26 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Mitchell, Joan, 1963-08-28 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ashbery, John, 1963-08-30 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Myers, John, 1963-09-01 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Neu, Renee, 1963-09-18 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1963-09-18 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1963-09-25 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - LeSueur, Joe, 1963-09-30 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Guest, Barbara (from Paris), 1963-10-14 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Goldberg, Mike (from Rome), 1963-11-11 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - LeSeur, Joe (from Belgrade), 1963-11-19 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Allen, Don (from Vienna), 1963-11-23 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Ashbery, John, 1964-01-21 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1964-01-23 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Berkson, Bill, 1964-01-27 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1964-02-03 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1964-02-13 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hornick, Lita, 1964-02-17 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Grosman, Tanya, 1964-02-18 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1964-03-26 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Rivers, Larry, 1964-04-18 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Cremer, Jan, 1964-05-08 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Cremer, Jan, 1964-05-08 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1964-06-05 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1964-06-24 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - New York Review of Books, 1964-06-30 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1964-07-02 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1964-08-29 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1964-09-08 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1964-09-18 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1964-10-12 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Goldberg, Mike, 1964-10-22 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Goldberg, Mike, 1964-11-16 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Goldberg, Mike, 1964-11-28 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Neu, Renee, 1965-03-31 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence, 1965-02-28 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ashbery, John, 1965-04-26 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Larson, Jack and Jim Bridges, 1965-08-16 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Open Letter on Erje Ayden, 1965-12-20 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Ceravolo, Joe, 1966-03-04 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1966-03-24 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Warren, Vincent (from Arnhem), 1966-05-10 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Mitchell, Joan (from Arnhem), 1966-05-15 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Berkson, Bill, 1966-05-24 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Newman, Barnett, 1966-07-15 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Warren, Vincent, 1966-07-16 (Box 3, Folder 32)